You’ll sweat blood!
Death Spa is a horror film directed by Michael Fischa.
Michael's health club is beseiged with a series of terrible murders
involving killer saunas and other grisly devices.
Michael's wife killed herself a while before and her
brother holds Michael responsible.
Michael needs to stop the bloodshed before he loses all of his clients.
Michael Evans, played by William Bumiller.
Laura Danvers, played by Brenda Bakke.
Catherine, played by Shari Shattuck.
Marvin, played by Ken Foree.
David Avery, played by Merritt Butrick.
Tom, played by Robert Lipton.
Death Spa is a 1988 American supernatural slasher film directed by Michael Fischa and starring William Bumiller,
Brenda Bakke, Merritt Butrick, Ken Foree, Karyn Parsons, Rosalind Cash, and Vanessa Bell Calloway.
Its plot follows a series of mysterious deaths occurring in a high-tech Los Angeles health spa, resulting from
the spirit of the owner's deceased wife, who possesses the club's intricate computer system.
In Europe and Asia, the film was released under
the alternative title Witch Bitch.
Butrick's role in the film was his last before his death, while
Parsons's role marked her feature film debut as an actress.
The film explores themes of murder, spa, health club.
The tone is dark.